[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：让我们将它与伪经典模型进行比较。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So let's compare this to the pseudoclassical model.
所以你记得这个。
So you remember this.
有这么多东西在周围晃荡真是太可怕了。
It's just awful with all this stuff hanging around.
所以现在这个功能模型中，这是相同的事情。
So this is the same thing now in this functional model.
而且代码变得更干净了。
And the code gets a lot cleaner.
首先，我们没有.原型的东西挂在末端。
For one thing, we don't have the .prototype stuff hanging off the end.
一切都很好，整洁，包含在这里。
Everything is nice and neat and contained within here.
所以gizmo构造函数非常简单，它只是返回一个新对象。
So the gizmo constructor very simple, it's simply returning a new object.
请注意，花括号位于右侧。
Notice the curly braces are on the right.
所以这会很好用的。
So this is gonna work perfectly.
我们不是说this.id等于id，而是简单地说id：id，我们就完成了。
Instead of saying this.id equals id, we simply say id:id and we're done.
然后我们的名人堂将会制作一个新的小玩意儿。
Then our who's it is going to make a new gizmo.
然后我们将向该函数添加我们的测试方法或
And we're then going to add to that function our test method or
将我们的测试方法添加到该对象中。
add to that object our test method.
返回对象，它就完成了。
Return the object and it's done.
所以代码也变得简单了很多。
So the code got a lot simpler as well.
是吗？&gt；&gt；演讲者2：我想大约十分钟
Yeah? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I think about ten minutes
以前，你说不要用这个，或者你不推荐，或者
ago, you were saying not to use this, or that you didn't recommend it or
就算是喜欢。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，
even like it. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah,
这是下一步。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
that's the next step. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：那么让我们假设
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So let's suppose we
想要有隐私
want to have privacy,
这是我认为在对象系统中非常重要的东西。
which is something that I think is very important to have in object systems.
所以我们可能有一个目标，只有这样才能获得访问权限
So that we may have a goal where the only way to get access
到ID是通过对象的方法
to the ID is through the methods of the object
我们不希望任何人能够访问ID，除非通过方法。
that we don't want anybody to be able to access ID except through the methods.
JavaScript在经典模型中没有提供任何隐私的方式，
JavaScript doesn't provide any way of having privacy in the classical model,
在伪经典模型中，因为你附加到一个对象上的一切
in the pseudo-classical model, because everything you attach to an object
对访问该对象的任何人都可见。
is visible to anybody who gets access to the object.
所以那里没有隐私。
So there's no privacy there.
但是函数模型，因为我们在闭包中有函数作用域，所以我们这样做。
But the functional model, because we have functions scope in closure, we do.
假设我们想隐藏ID。
So let's say we want to hide the IDs.
只能通过两种字符串测试方法获取ID。
You can only get ID through the two string test methods.
代码实际上变得更简单了。
The code actually gets simpler.
所以这里我们不说this.id，而是简单地说id，
So instead of saying this.id here we simply say id,
我们得到它，我们将关闭传入的变量。
and we're getting it from, we're closing over the variable that got passed in.
所以这是私人的，完全是私人的。
So it's private, it's completely private.
而且这个代码也变得更简单了。
And this code got simpler too.
我们拿到了这个ID，再一次，我们要结束了
We got this ID, and which again, we're getting through closure and
代码变得更小更简单。
the code got smaller and simpler.
是啊。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：难道功能没有被复制，
Yeah. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Aren't the functions copied,
但是，那么对于每个实例？&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：对，
though, then for each instance? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right,
因此，这种模式是有成本的。
so there is a cost to this model.
在原型模型中我们节省了内存，
That in the prototypal model we're saving memory,
因为每个实例只有一个方法。
because we only have one of each method per instance.
在这一个中，我们将创建更多的函数对象。
In this one we're going to have lots more function objects being created.
我们周五会更多地讨论这个，但事实证明
And we'll talk more about this on Friday, but it turns out that
只有当您拥有数百万个实例时，这一点才有意义。
that's significant only if you've got millions of instances.
记忆变得如此庞大，
That memory has become so expansive,
你的口袋里有千兆字节的RAM。
you've got gigabytes of RAM in your pocket.
基于内存保护做出重要的架构决策
Making important architectural decisions based on memory conservation
现在不是一个好的选择。
is not a good way to go now.
我认为如果你担心数以百万计的情况，
And I would contend that if you are worried about millions of instances,
也许这不是你应该使用的语言。
maybe this is not the language you should be using.
但对于我们所做的大部分事情，
But for most of what we do,
你将要制造的物体的数量将会相对较少。
the number of objects that you're gonna make is gonna be relatively small.
就性能而言，这会很棒的。
And performance-wise, this is gonna be great.
所以我们会在建筑上花更多的钱，但是
So we're gonna spend a little bit more in construction, but
我们在执行上的花费会少很多。
we're gonna spend a lot less in execution.
所以我认为这是一场胜利。&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：您创建的事实
So I think it's a win. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That fact that you create
对象的每个实例的该函数的实例，
an instance of that function for each instance of the object,
那是因为结束了对吧？
that's because of closure, right?
如果没有那个我们就不能结束。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：那是
If we can't have closure without that. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: That's
好吧。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
right. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，因为
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah, because of
结束，我们愿意付出这个代价。
closure, we're willing to pay that cost.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Right. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: And
这不是很大的成本。
it's not much of a cost.
如果您查看函数对象中的内容，
If you look at what is in a function object,
基本上有一个对象，其中有两个额外的指针。
there is basically an object with two extra pointers in it.
一个用于指向代码的指针，以及
One for the pointer to the code, and
一个是指向创建功能的激活的指针。
one the pointer to the activation of the creating function.
里面没什么别的了。
There's not much else in there.
将有一个到原型对象的链接，
There will be a link to the prototype object,
这是一种浪费，因为我们不打算使用它。
which is a waste because we're not going to use that.
就是这样。所以
That's it. So,
这些东西没有太多的内存，初始化它们的工作也不多。
there's not much memory in those things, not a lot of work to initialize them.
所以它很轻。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：有人吗
So it's very lightweight. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Anybody
其他？&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以这也是
else? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So this also
解决了我们在语言中遇到的与此绑定相关的另一个问题。
solves another problem that we have in the language which is related to this binding.
这就是古老的hoozit，最初的伪古典hoozit。
So this is the old hoozit, the original pseudo-classical hoozit.
假设我们想要将测试函数从对象中取出。
Suppose we want to take the test function out of the object.
我们可以这样做，因为您可以从对象中复制任何对象引用，并且
Which we can do because you can copy any object reference out of an object and
将其放在一个单独的变量中，然后将该变量作为函数调用。
put it in a separate variable, and then call that variable as a function.
该调用将失败，因为当我们将test作为函数调用时，
That call will fail because when we call test as a function,
这将不会绑定到它所来自的对象，而是
this will be bound not to the object that it came from but
到其他对象，或者是全局对象，或者是未定义的对象。
to something else, either to the global object or undefined.
这两种情况中的任何一种都会导致测试失败。
Either of which will cause this test to fail.
但是在新的形式中，因为我们的方法中没有这一点，所以我们可以
But in the new form because our methods do not have this in them, we can
获取这些函数，将它们从对象中拉出，并独立调用它们，以及
take those functions, pull them out of the object, and call them independently, and
它们仍然以完全相同的方式工作，因为它们不依赖于此。
they still work exactly the same way because they don't depend on this.
因此，无论如何调用这些方法，它们都将始终正确工作。
So no matter how those methods are called, they will always work correctly.
所有这方面的脆弱性都是完全避免的。
All the fragileness of this is completely avoided.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我想说清楚这一点，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Just so I'm clear on this,
在中间，在您要获取测试ID的函数中，
in the middle one there, in your function where you're taking the Test ID,
您可以访问ID，因为它被推到堆上，
you have access to ID because it was pushed onto the heap,
它还没有被垃圾收集
and it hasn't been garbage collected yet
因为它植根于某个地方。
because it's rooted somewhere.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：对。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：好的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，事实上，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah, in fact,
它是由那个物体扎根的。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：是的。
it's being rooted by that object. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：或者用那种方法。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Or by that method.
只要那个方法还存在，
As long as that method survives,
它需要的环境也将继续存在。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：好的。
the context it needs will also survive. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Okay.